

# Sales operations and economist

remal.natourr@gmail.com 0790336578

Amman, Jordan

# Remal Alnatour

#### **Profile**

Passionate sales operations and management

Worked in retail as sales associates for 5 years with full energetic work and 3 months of training as sales agent in MetLife insurance, in this five years I got promoted many times and finally ended as assistant manager. and in the 3 months I've collected many new knowledge.

I am seeking an opportunities to improve my skills and experience

# **Employment History**

Customer service at Sales person , social media and online agent , Amman

04/2019-09/2020

Head cashiers and supervisor at Cashier supervisor, Amman

10/2021-11/2022

Assistant manager at Trainee assistant manager,
Amman

12/2022-06/2023

Sales agent at MetLife insurance at Sales agent , Amman

11/2023-Present

#### Education

2.49 , Hashemite university , Az Zarqā

02/2018-09/2023

Graduated as economist student

#### Links

Facebook

### Skills

Decision Making	5/5
Ability to Multitask	5/5
Highly Organized	5/5
Highly Motivated	5/5
Leadership	
Good Communication	5/5
Customer Service	5/5
Collaboration & Teamwork	5/5

# Languages

Arabic	Native speaker
English	Highly proficient
French	C2

## References

Amman mehyar from Daraghmeh Ammarmehyar92@gmail.com +962 7 9992 4787

Mohammed adeeb from Daraghmeh Mohammedaddeb@gmail.com 0788800575